CONTACTS



alikirilovz@gmail.com



+994554764284

DETAILS



GitHub



<u>Linkedin</u>



Portfolio

HARD SKILLS

- OS Administration
- Database management
- System administration
- **Network Administration**
- Virtualization
- · Networking skills
- Cloud services
- Project management

LANGUAGE

- English
- Russian
- Turkish
- Azerbaijan

ABOUT ME

Determined and devoted IT specialist with a deep interest in programming and networking technologies. My passion for the IT industry drives me to continuously develop and improve in this field. Selfassurance enables me to effectively solve technical challenges and strive for new accomplishments.

Ali Kirilov

Network Administrator

WORK EXPERIENCE

Globus Center

Baku

Dec 2022 - Present

Globus Center

Oct 2021 - Dec 2022

Globus Center

Baku

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

Network Administrator

Network Administrator Assistant

IT Support

EDUCATION

KYIV NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND DESIGN

Kviv

Oct 2023 - Present

SKILLS

Network

Administration

Network setup and administration, Router and switch configuration, Network security, Network monitoring and management, Server administration, Automation and scripting, Backup and data recovery, Wireless network management, Certifications (e.g., Cisco CCNA, CCNP), Troubleshooting and collaboration with colleagues.

Programming

I have experience in website development using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, as well as knowledge of PHP. Additionally, I have experience in creating mobile applications using Java in Android Studio.

I have also worked on projects involving the development of a voice assistant using Python and website management systems using Diango.

I possess skills in managing databases with languages such as Oracle SQL, PostgreSQL, SQL *Plus, and PL/SQL, MySQL.

CERTIFICATES

- · Cisco Network Security: Core Security Concepts
- Prepare for the Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) (200-301)
- Advanced SQL
- · Git, GitHub & GitHub Actions
- **Microsoft Power BI**
- Oracle SQL